Good afternoon Good afternoon I am from Ukraine
добрый день Добрый день Я из Украины
Khmelnitsky city of a human city of Russia
город Хмельницкий людского города России
Where are you from again Ukraine
Откуда вы еще раз Украина город
Khmelnitsky city And what city of Russia are
Хмельницкий А вы с какого города России
you from I understood from Novosibirsk how the
Я из Новосибирска понял как у вас там
weather is
погода
normal there Cold how many minuses
нормально Холодно сколько минусов
minus 30 is somewhere about as tough as you
минус 30 где-то примерно жестяк как вы
are Go out to  street Well, yes, I’m already -30, the
там Выходите на улицу Ну да я уже -30
humidity is great support for a
нас влажность большая поддержка
special military operation
специального военную операцию
Well, yes, I understand the military registration and enlistment office already went there
Ну да понял военкомат уже ходили
No, but because I’m a student I do
Нет а что потому что я студент мне
n’t need to go there, I understand that you
незачем туда ходить я понял то есть вы
support other people in Ukraine to die
поддержите чтобы дохли в Украине другие
yes
люди да
Well, how can I tell you in-  firstly, there is no
Ну как вам сказать во-первых нету
objective goal of this special operation, no one
объективной цели этой спецоперации никто
knows for sure what it is for if
точно не знает ради чего она идет если
you don’t know the goal
вы не знаете цели
and you don’t support it, I know ours from the point of
а вы не поддерживаете я знаю наш с точки
view of our goal, it is necessary that the Russian
зрения нашей цели надо чтобы русские
troops get the hell out of Ukraine
войска свалили нафиг с Украины
unambiguously from the point of view of our goal, we
однозначно с точки зрения нашей цели нам
need NATO not  came to you and
надо чтобы НАТО не пришло к вам и
look, this is the joke. You
смотрите вот в чем прикол Вы же
understand that after 91 years when the
понимаете что после 91 года когда
Soviet Union collapsed America, the
Советский Союз развалила Америка
Americans established control over  by all the
американцы установили контроль над всеми
governments of the republics So the
правительствами республик Так
post-Soviet, including over the Ukrainian one,
постсоветский в том числе над украинской
that we can decide if they put the president on us
что мы можем решать если они нам ставят
, the
президента
Supreme Council and so on does not accept,
Верховный Совет и так далее не принимает
and instead of attacking
и вы вместо того чтобы напасть на
America or England, you bomb our
Америку или Англию вы бомбите наш
fraternal Slavic people
братские славянский народ Харьков
Russian-speaking Kharkov
русскоязычный
But why would I ask this  the question is, I
Но почему бы мне задаете этот вопрос я
’m somehow personally connected with Putin If
что как-то лично с Путиным связано Если
you don’t support me, I don’t support this
вы не поддержите я вам не за два этот
question,
вопрос
but you think there is a choice Well, look, I don’t
а вы думаете есть выбор Ну смотрите не
support the killing of Slavs by the Slavs.
поддерживает убийство славянами Славян
you have this Bandera movement
там у вас это бандеровщина началась
started I have relatives from Ukraine They
У меня есть родственники из Украины Они
were killed
убиты были
that in fact in what city
что на самом деле в каком городе
in Odessa in Odessa in the 90s they killed
в Одессе в Одессе в 90-х годах убивали
Russians but how Well, it’s not straight that they
русских но как Ну не прям чтобы их
were somehow persecuted, they tracked
как-то преследовали выслеживал
down, but you have signs of Nazism
выслеживали но признаки нацизма у вас
were [ __ ] here Odessa Yuri
были [__] вот Одесский Юрий
Bandera monuments
памятники Бандера
Odessa nineties to me Because they
Одесса девяностых мне Потому что от меня
probably hid this story from me, I was in
наверное скрывали это историю я вот в
Odessa  I understand why some
Одессе был я понял почему там некоторые
Russians there are afraid to say the score in Russian
русские боятся по-русски говорить счет
I don’t remember 90 this is the Odessa Massacre remember
не помню 90 это Одесская Резня помните
there was the Odessa massacre in 90 91
было там Одесская резняк 90 91 году
when the Soviet Union collapsed, I understood
когда Советский Союз развалился я понял
there were Russians rising on the Potemkin area
там было на потемкинской местности
And these Bandera people drove them,
русские поднимались А эти бандеровцы их
threw up the Potemkin
погнали подбрасывались потемкинской
stairs, and also a documentary
лестнице еще и документальный фильм
remember the film
помните
back then, this president
тогда еще этот президент
in Poland, Janusz-Jinsky So even then he
в Польше януш-джинский Так он еще тогда
condemned this Odessa massacre,
осудил вот эту одесскую резню
what do you say correctly to this,
что на это скажете
I say Andrei Popik pop and yes
правильно говорю Андрей Попик поп и да
Well,
Ну и
but nothing, but I kind of don’t know
но ничего но я как бы не в курсе насчет
about this documentary
вот этой вот этого документального
film I came up with  on the go gossip about
фильма придумал на ходу сплетал про
children's life
детской жизни
eat on the go gossip about the president's children's rubber
есть на ходу сплетал про детскую резину
invented In short,
президента придумал Короче
but I say that I don't know About
но я и говорю что я не в курсе Насчет
that documentary What you
того документального фильма О чем вы
're talking about, I'm just wondering I don't
говорите мне просто интересно не в курсе
know that in Odessa in the nineties
того что в Одессе в девяностых щели
Russian gaps are what they are  - it’s a joke, but not
русских это вообще какой-то прикол но не
massively straight. I’m talking about single people in the
массово прям Я же говорю одиночных в
entrance of someone
подъезде кого-то
Well, it’s not that they gave in the entrance But in  in general,
Ну не то чтобы в подъезде дали Но вообще
there were such signs that there,
признаки такие были что там
not only in Odessa, in general, in the nineties, in
не только в Одессе вообще в девяностых в
Odessa, they erected a monument to cooper, as
Одессе поставили памятник бондаре так
I understand it, not in the nineties, but
понимаю не в девяностых А вот на
today they
сегодняшний
erected a monument to
поставили памятник Бандера
Bandera.
А где можно
-x badge is
родственники рассказывали в 90-х бляха
real
реально
Well, how is it connected that's what you are
Ну а как это связано вот что вы сейчас
saying now what we said that
говорите то что говорили мы начали что
it was there and Odessa twisted the Russians there they
этого там так и Одесса кручу русских там
pinched back in 90 Well, you skewered in this
щемили еще в 90 Ну вот вы шпилили в этот
plane, I want to clarify where in
плоскости я вас Хочу уточнить где там в
Odessa who is there from  Russians were pinched, how
Одессе кого там из русских защемили как
is the memory of Odessa residents, probably if they
там памятение Одесситы наверно если
hear at all,
услышат вообще
but not only in Odessa
но не только что в Одессе
Let's finish from Odessa, then in Odessa there
Давайте с Одессы закончим то в Одессе
were monuments to coopers or there were no
были памятники бондари или не было
90s, maybe there wasn’t, but now at the
90-х может и не было но сейчас на данный
moment I saw they put it And where can you
момент видел поставили А где вот можете
say let it be there  a friend will google While we
сказать пусть там друг погуглит Пока мы
are talking about the monument to Bandera in Odessa,
говорим памятник бандери в Одессе
I saw the news that in Ukraine in
я увидел новость то что в Украине в
some city they were going to erect a
каком-то городе собирались поставить
monument to Bandera Yes  and, accordingly
Да памятник Бандера и соответственно
, the
никак не связан
pancake put me to sleep in no way. You said that a
блин усыпил меня ты говорил что в Одессе
monument to Bandera was being erected in Odessa. You
ставят памятник Бандера Ты же это сказал
didn’t invent it.
не придумал
I say that I had relatives from
Я говорю что у меня родственники из
Odessa, they put a monument there.
Одессы были они памятник там ставили ты
nifiga it’s not clear,
вспомнили вообще нифига не понятно
come on, so your relatives from Odessa
давай так что из Одессы ваши
told what it was
родственники рассказали что там было
like 90
такое 90
[laugh]
[смех]
Damn,
Блин
so rust is shorter in the chat Who will create and
так ржа короче в чате Кто создаст и типа
put a plus sign like the
поставьте плюсик типа
90s memorable Bondar
90-х памятных Бондарь
[music]
[музыка]
mines are shorter than the
мин короче стоит
Odessa Reznyanskaya stairs
Одесская резнянская лестница
Yak can be like that  and stupid here is a
Як можно будто таким и тупыми вот
badge-people live to be 30 Rocky for example
бляха-люды доживают до 30 Рокки например